http://www.sellersourcebook.com/w3c/privacy.php

Privacy
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used at Seller Sourcebook. We take
extraordinary steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection
Seller Sourcebook is the sole owner of the information collected from our website. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Seller Sourcebook uses cookies only for login convenience of our subscribers.
Log Files
Seller Sourcebook keeps log files on broad fields to analyze trends and gather data for basic demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitor's
personal identification.
Sharing
Seller Sourcebook does not share any visitor or subscriber information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.
Links
Links to other sites outside of Seller Sourcebook do not apply to this privacy statement. We are not responsible for privacy policies of other websites linked to Seller Sourcebook.
Please read the privacy statement of each website linked to Seller Sourcebook for information and data use for visitor's personal identification. Our privacy statement applies solely
Seller Sourcebook.
Changes of our Policy
If and when our policy statement changes, subscribers will be notified of the changes, and provided a link to this page to view the changes. If a subscriber decides that our policy does not benefit them, they may opt-out option at anytime.
